Gülsüm Erbay

Software Developer

I am a software developer for 5+ years. I have both frontend and backend experience. I'm doing my best to get results in my projects on time. I always pay attention to SOLID principles and make sure my code understandable, readable and clean. I love learning and I'm really learn quickly. I am a person who enjoys develop algorithms and software.



glsm.erbay@gmail.com

gulsumerbay.com

linkedin.com/in/gulsumerbay in

github.com/gulsumerbay 👩

EDUCATION

Master's Degree in Computer Engineering Kocaeli University

09/2014 - 12/2018

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering Kocaeli University

09/2019 - 06/2013

WORK EXPERIENCE

RMira Teknoloji A.Ş. Software Developer

KOCAELİ

I have developed CRM software revisions for car rental companies. The company was providing real-time vehicle tracking services and manufacturing embedded vehicle tracking equipment. I developed the modules of the vehicle tracking software. I worked Full Stack with VueJS and .Net Core. I rewrote the modules written in .Net with Clean Architecture architecture in .Net Core. I also ensured that Redis, SignalR, Mediatr Pattern technologies were used in the projects and tests were carried out with XUnit. In addition, I prepared a vehicle tracking animation on the Google API using Vue.js and Leaflet in the frontend section.

PremierTurk Information Technologies Software Developer

09/2019 - 03/2020

I took part in web applications used in municipalities. Database I wrote revisions, frontend with AngularJS, backend in .Net Web API project. In addition, I improved myself by creating reports with Telerik Report Designer and making revisions in the admin panel.

Proser Information Technologies Software Developer

KOCAELİ

I have worked on website and e-commerce applications for various clients. I gained experience with web interfaces using MVC .Net, HTML, Javascript.

MapSOFT Software Informatics LLC Intern/Junior Software Developer

KOCAELİ

With C # Winforms and Xamarin Android, Location Based Information Systems software (CAD, GIS, KBS, Municipal Automation), Digital Cadastre Program revisions were made. Applications were improved with Devexpress integration. FireBird, SQLite, Access, PostgreSQL database management and data transfer panels between them. Opening GIS file types such as KML / KMZ, GeoJSON on Google Maps Api and preparing interfaces. Rewriting CAD applications written for desktop with Xamarin Android on mobile. Extracting datas with FastReport.

Çelik Halat ve Tel Sanayi A.Ş. Summer Internship

08/2012 - 09/2012

KOCAELİ

Izmit Municipality Summer Internship

KOCAFLİ

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Better learning Mediatr pattern, XUnit, design patterns Basic application coding and Clean Architecture implementation.

Vue.js, .Net Core

E-Commerce application and product management using Trendyol and Hepsiburada integrations.

Vue.js, .Net Core

Coding of TODO list application using Vue.js for frontend, .NET Core for backend and MSSQL for database

Vue.js, .Net Core, MSSQL

Master's thesis project: Precise Agricultural Productivity calculation with GIS and GPS. Product data crud operations on Android device.

Xamarin Android, SQLite

Experimental application by creating location finding algorithms and solutions with RFID in master's degree.

Winforms C#

Virtual Classroom Application. Creating course selections and exam schedules with the relational database.

ASP .Net, SQL Server

Coding of TODO list application using Angular.js for frontend, .NET Core for backend and MSSQL for database.

Angular.js, .NET Core, MSSQL

Creating 2011 Eurovision song contest sessions with Welch-Powel Coloring Algorithm.

Dev C++

Word hunt puzzle solving application.

Simulation application creating new circuits using basic logic gates or new circuits.

Winforms C#.

REFERENCES

Emin Berberoğlu

MapSoft Software Informatics LLC - General manager.

Bahadır Denizli

PremierTurk Information Technologies - Senior Software Developer

LANGUAGES

English - Upper Intermediate Professional Working Proficiency